Just 24 hours are given.
The directors who will head to the third Last Stage...
are JEONG MIN JUN, Simeez,
BADA, and INGYOO.
The required condition for this Last Stage: 24H...
is the umbrella.
This is crazy.
No way.
This is driving me crazy.
I wanted to give up at that moment.
(Prove yourself within 24 hours if you wish to survive.)
I will bloom a flower on this stage.
I can definitely survive.
I must pour out everything I have.
Losing is not an option for me.
I've still got it.
How was this thought of in 24 hours?
They're determined for this.
Won't I have the biggest advantage?
This is my home ground.
The introduction genius!
It made me think, "Could I have thought of that?"
That was how good the performance was.
I really enjoyed it.
The one to be eliminated from the third Last Stage...
is...
This is so tough.
I panicked a lot.
It's very sad.
(Who will survive after the third Last Stage?)
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(Last Stage: 24H)
Just 24 hours are given.
A competition for survival with the title of director on the line.
Last Stage: 24H.
Another competition for survival will happen again today.
This is the condition for this Last Stage: 24H.
It's...
the umbrella.
The umbrella is an item we are very familiar with...
made to cover us from the rain.
However,
when umbrellas meet stage lights and video images,
they become a field of flowers,
(A field of flowers)
an endless desert,
(An endless desert)
a digital space,
(Digital world)
and even a new world.
(A new world)
They turn into an objet...
that creates many different moments.
Even with the same umbrellas,
the way they are interpreted and used...
will create completely different stories and performances.
There are four directors who will be...
in this intense competition for survival.
(Last Stage: 24H)
Skills of a top-tier player...
and outstanding directing abilities.
The complete director who is capable of everything,
BADA.
I can definitely survive.
I will move to the next step right away.
With unique concepts...
and smart usage of props,
this concept master...
constantly creates new scenes.
Simeez.
I must pour out everything I have.
I have to show everyone who Simeez is.
With trendy styles...
and tasty performances,
this director creates a bang out of nowhere.
INGYOO.
It will be hard to beat me.
I want people to see my performance as soon as possible.
He does his storytelling through dancing and performances.
The director who creates a work of art on stage,
JEONG MIN JUN.
I thought that I would definitely survive.
I tend to have this groundless sense of confidence...
whenever I perform during the Last Stage.
How have these four directors...
created their performances with their directing abilities?
Now, the third Last Stage: 24H will begin.
Ready?
Fight!
(Last Stage: 24H)
(Who will survive the Last Stage?)
We're all heading out together.
The lineup is incredible.
This is crazy.
We can battle each other again fair and square.
I hoped that MIN JUN wouldn't have to go.
It was my third time going through this.
I can't really describe this feeling.
I feel desperate and disappointed.
It's devastating.
It feels like I'm always going with the wrong strategies.
Even during the mega mission,
I went with a reckless plan...
even though an objet wasn't needed.
"I'm not a strategist."
It feels like nothing is working out for me in this competition.
I can't imagine myself performing on stage.
Well,
(The atmosphere is heavy in BADA's room.)
I think I gave up...
as soon as I saw my score.
It made me doubt my abilities.
As there were so many talented directors,
I felt a limit.
I felt ashamed of myself.
I believe that Directors' War...
is a huge opportunity.
That is why...
I wish to make the most of it.
I don't want to leave any regrets.
I wish for my work or dancing...
to be able to...
move hearts once again.
I will work my socks off again to make that happen.
The train for the elimination battle is ready to depart!
It was disappointing.
(INGYOO: 7th)
It was a rank I had never received before.
It felt like a nightmare.
Not even a silly dream would be this bad.
But this is reality.
I feel greatly disappointed.
I wish the ones who worked with us...
will realize that the good moments we shared together...
matter the most.
I'm worried...
that this would break their heart.
I did wish that MIN JUN wouldn't have to participate.
(A fake laugh)
(Screaming)
(Flapping)
(Punches of anger)
Gosh, it's MIN JUN's third time.
He's going to become a master.
This is...
tough.
Placing first in the team...
didn't feel that pleasant.
The reality is that I was the head of a snake...
that got knocked out by the tail of a dragon...
and ended up in the Last Stage.
In total,
I'll be working for 72 hours for every Last Stage: 24H.
Won't I have the biggest advantage in the Last Stage?
This is my home ground.
It's like a lineup for the final round.
(It's like a lineup for the final round.)
I will create something to make me win.
I'll put my soul into this.
I must beat them all.
The girls are going to be in tears and snot again.
Feeling pressure is inevitable.
I will do my best...
to burn myself up for this.
I will survive.
I don't care who gets eliminated.
I will survive no matter what.
(The choreography practice begins for the Last Stage.)
(Screaming)
(Knocked down)
This is crazy.
I'm scared.
(Black and white umbrellas lined up in perfect order)
Hey, umbrellas.
Are you ready?
Have you all warmed up?
Not yet? Let's get warmed up.
You're still a bit stiff. Okay.
Are you ready? Let's begin.
(The Last Stage is this dangerous.)
(BADA gets to her senses and checks the umbrellas first.)
I have a bad memory about umbrellas.
It happened during "Street Woman Fighter 2."
During the Battle Performance,
we had to use umbrellas.
It felt like a routine was performed with the umbrellas in the hands.
We weren't able to overcome...
- the umbrella performance.
- The umbrella performance.
I have a memory of being destroyed.
I had given up on umbrellas at that moment.
But now, I must work with umbrellas again.
I will use them well this time...
and prove to everyone...
that I have changed.
I must overcome it.
I can't live with that memory forever.
I decided to think differently.
As this could be my final performance in Directors' War,
it will be a "happy ending."
I will use the umbrellas for that.
Umbrellas...
only made me feel depressed.
I wish for the umbrellas to be filled with happy memories.
As soon as I saw the umbrella,
I thought it looked like the petals of a flower.
I thought of ways to utilize that.
I kept thinking of ideas...
while trying to get closer to the umbrellas.
Like this.
(Blooming)
It's like a flower bud, right?
The inside part of a rose.
There must be a lot of these.
There must be a lot on both sides.
It's like a flower bud when they are placed together.
They look like flower petals when they are spread out.
I'm planning to express them as fancy bouquets.
The beam projector will be used on the umbrellas.
Flowers can be displayed on them.
There's a special feature with the beam projector.
I wanted roses to be displayed.
I wanted to paint the stage with flowers.
The dancers have to use their senses when using the umbrellas.
It can't be marked...
like a regular choreography part.
The details of the umbrellas...
and the angles of the umbrellas.
We did our best to work on those parts.
Could you focus on the angle?
It's like this right now.
You must hold the handle.
(The members of Team BADA start working as one with the umbrellas.)
There we go!
Nice!
You look incredible!
The concept is "Bloom."
The concept itself gave me a lot of courage.
I am someone who will survive from the rainstorm.
I will come back...
and confidently secure my ticket to the semi-finals.
Hello.
(Simeez, practice room)
Oh, gosh. Here we go again.
How many are there?
Is this a dream?
The umbrellas were lined up in a scary way.
Oh, I'm going to lose it.
Can I do this today?
(Sighing)
It was overwhelming at first.
It felt like I walked into it...
when I wasn't ready for it.
I'm going to lose it.
(In despair)
Everyone is excited, actually.
How will Simeez use...
these umbrella objets?
I shouldn't have used objets in the first mission.
Oh, objets...
Anyway, I'm confident about objets.
I'm pretty confident about using objets.
To list ones I've used...
Lights, cloths, various tables.
I've also used various chairs.
Mirrors, frames, arrows.
I'm seriously going to lose it.
I can't just do kind of well. I need to absolutely kill it...
to keep my word.
I'm feeling all sorts of pressure.
I felt that I had to think of something.
So...
I want to be on top like this.
But if you go on top, these things...
But use several of these.
- Shall we try to lift you?
- Yes.
- One, two, three.
- Hold on tight.
- Oh, my.
The umbrellas...
If not...
(You need to be original, Simeez.)
- Oh, flip it inside out?
- Yes.
(Slap!)
Like this. Isn't this side more comfortable?
Use 3 or 4 and put me on top.
- Maybe consider physics?
- It won't work, right?
- I quit.
- Should we put your feet here?
I feel so much pressure. Objets...
What should we do?
It's my first time at Last Stage,
but I saw that you're more likely to win if you can create...
that wow factor with objets.
I need to make something enormous with the umbrellas.
I'm going to slightly hang off of him like this.
Then you'll make wings on my back.
Fold, open, fold, open.
Doing that looked like wings flapping.
I wanted it to look...
like wings opening up...
by opening the umbrellas.
Open, open, open, open.
(Opening asynchronously)
The timing will be very important.
We're not together.
(First, they practice to get the timing right.)
We're not together, everyone.
The speed I wanted...
I wanted it to be all together.
It was very hard to get the timing of opening and closing right.
Even if we're slightly off, it's so noticeable.
So let's keep practicing so we don't make mistakes.
One, two, three, four.
That was late just now. Again.
We only had 24 hours to practice.
- We'll do it until we get it right.
- Okay.
We synchronized everything. Until the end.
Seven, eight. One, two, three, four.
There we go. Perfect.
"Simeez is good at this sort of thing."
I wanted to show people that.
(Team INGYOO, practice room)
(Laughing creepily)
Then to the back.
(Who are these people crowding the practice room?)
I want to get started.
Where are you, INGYOO?
Let's each take a spot and act cool.
Where is INGYOO?
(Ta-da)
(The main character is here.)
(Woo, woo, woo, woo. It loosely means "Welcome.")
Here we are. We're here.
Welcome on board, everyone.
You see these, right?
I want to get rid of them.
Why umbrellas?
Let's give it a go.
Let's just get started.
I didn't really have a concept.
But for Last Stage, we needed a concept.
The objet is priority.
I figured the outcome will really depend on how we use it.
So we used the umbrellas in various ways.
We flipped them, made stabbing motions.
Even if it's a bit childish, I wanted it to have impact.
Or maybe play up the mood of the song...
and use it like a tail, like an animal.
(Bobbing his head)
(Loving it)
That's hilarious.
Kind of "Madagascar" vibes.
Hold on.
I'm not confident about making it animal-themed.
Let's try it as people.
How should the opening be?
We need to show the concept in the intro.
So I thought very carefully about the opening.
What should we do?
If we're using props, we have to do something with them.
Try placing them like a ladder.
We were thinking of making a bridge sort of thing...
and crossing it.
It's weird.
Pass!
Pass.
The story isn't flowing.
So I was thinking about it.
Are you an umbrella seller? Wholesale?
Six, seven, eight.
Let's give out umbrellas one by one, like a factory.
Go, go, go. It's fun.
Ours is the most fun.
We got in a circle. And three.
And four. And five.
Nice. Very nice.
So we made an impactful intro.
Then suddenly, the umbrellas looked like swords.
Distribute swords...
Distribute swords and go on a mission?
That's visually nice too.
Should we be ninjas?
That's amazing.
(Going right into character)
That's new. No one has done this.
Using umbrellas as ninjas...
There's something here. I think we can do something.
Like ninjas that use sorcery.
You think they're swords, but suddenly,
they turn out to be umbrellas. That kind of thing.
We're on a mission, but then we start to fly.
We created a character that can have fun,
even while on a mission.
What I'm sure of is that it'll be fun.
If we mix Asian culture and my otaku-ness,
that'll create synergy.
I've been doing things last minute all my life.
This time, swordsmanship came to me at the last minute.
(Team JEONG MIN JUN, practice room)
Objet.
(JEONG MIN JUN dives into studying the objet.)
Out of all props we had so far,
this is number one.
It's the hardest to use.
I want to break all of the umbrellas.
The table and cube were on the easy side.
Before, we could go on top of the props,
use them flipped over,
or use them as a backdrop.
But umbrellas...
have to be carried.
I thought we would lose points...
if we were carrying umbrellas and suddenly put them down to dance.
So the key for me was to use the umbrellas...
in a way that fit the story the best.
It can't just be creative. It needs to go with the story.
In "Last Stage," meaning is important.
Why did we use this prop this way?
Why did it have to be presented like this?
How convincing that is is the key.
Also, it's very important to use it in a unique way.
How can we create a dramatic effect?
Umbrellas...
How can I take this odd and difficult ingredient...
and cook it into something delicious?
I thought of weapons.
When guys are holding umbrellas,
we always have sword fights.
Hit the middle.
So you have to hold the end.
Like this. Sword fight.
I thought of war-related concepts.
I want to create a display...
of people in ancient history...
moving about at night before they head off to war.
Hit, then pull with them connected.
We tried using the hook of the umbrellas...
to make connections.
We tried jumping like long-armed monkeys.
Can you try making a bunker?
We tried creating various images.
But... I don't see a mood.
Our movements don't have a mood that connects to war.
Oh, no. It's too abstract.
Thinking about it as war is making it more difficult.
We did some ideation to broaden our minds.
I like the idea of flipping things inside out.
(Oh, my!)
- Oh, my.
- It worked.
(He successfully flipped the umbrella.)
(An unexpected discovery)
- Oh, that's cool.
- The last idea I had...
was to flip them inside out.
Then we happened to have a light.
The light reflects off of them.
It's like a torch.
Torches also have a fire in basket-like things.
I thought it would be appropriate to depict torches.
As someone who's been on Last Stage three times,
I thought my use of objets...
has been very good.
I'm going to survive this Last Stage no matter what.
(Last Stage D-Day)
- Hello.
They're displaying roses.
What is their concept? "The Rose of Versailles?"
Adjust the umbrella angle a bit, Yu Rim.
It's pretty. It's like a flower.
It looks like a flower bud.
To the audience,
it looks like an art wall.
It creates an impact before you get started.
Keep it like that,
and we'll do the beam projector.
Oh, they're lining each one up with a flower.
The numbering is very important here...
because they're projecting a flower...
on each one of your umbrellas.
So if we get this wrong, it'll all be off.
(Nervous)
I can see why BEBE is always so synchronized.
You're not in the right square.
(A dancer is not in line?)
(I think I'm in line...)
Ga Eun's row has to move 0.000001cm over.
How can you move 0.000001cm?
The slightest bit...
Do you just have to imagine moving?
(Glancing over)
They just did. I saw it.
- They just did?
- Yes.
You have to almost not move.
- Please remember that spot.
- Can you move back a bit?
Ready. Go.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six. Don't get too excited.
(The umbrella didn't close.)
Five and six. Again.
Sorry.
(Feeling bad)
I'm so sorry, but I can't let things slip anymore.
(Things suddenly get tense.)
I need you to wake up.
- Okay.
I think that was the most on edge I've been...
during all of Directors' War.
We got everything in sync in the practice room...
and came on set.
But everything fell apart.
Everyone was out of place and all.
I didn't know what to do.
Because if we don't do well, we have to go home.
If we don't get the details right for each and every person,
we'll definitely be eliminated.
I was worried they'd stop focusing,
so I needed to say something strong.
Get into formation and mark your numbers.
I'll give you five seconds to get into formation.
Five, four, three,
- two, one.
- Oh, my gosh.
(They got into formation in just 5 seconds.)
I think we got it. You can come down now.
After seeing them research some of these parts,
- I'm very excited.
- I think it'll look good.
Should we check the beam projector first?
(Checking the projection part at the start of rehearsal)
The projector is very big.
I think Simeez will be good at creating big pictures.
She has always liked using objets.
Hee Jung is good at using objets.
I was very excited about that.
Lights and special effects are very important.
So we checked those first.
(Checking the next projection)
(Shaking her head)
It's not visible right now.
It's too faint.
- It's too hard to see.
- This is the part.
(Wondering what to do)
When it comes to beam projectors,
you really need to control the lights well.
You really have to choose what to focus on.
And you always have to have a blackout.
The projection wasn't really visible.
I thought it'd be easier to see without the lights.
I want all the lights off for this part as well.
(Boldly turning the lights off)
- Good job.
- When we're using the projector,
we need to put the focus on the performance.
Those are hands. I think they're using hands.
I'm so curious what the concept is.
The choreography, the objet, the projection,
and the concept I chose.
I think it was most important to bring those things together.
Let's run it through with Simeez.
(They start to run through the performance.)
Are you ready? One, two.
She got on his back.
I think there's some sort of story.
Is she going somewhere?
"Simeez is good at this sort of thing."
I wanted to show people that.
I'll definitely come back.
That's cool.
(Getting into it)
(Oh, my.)
Nice.
Now what will INGYOO use?
Should we try running it?
- Okay.
Ninja?
Yes, like a ninja.
INGYOO never does cliche things.
So I'm very excited.
Is all of WE DEM BOYZ here?
Stretch your hamstrings. Hinge at the hips.
Your head should touch the floor.
You need to loosen up more.
I pushed them...
to get into their best physical conditions.
- The part with the spotlight.
- Yes?
Can you turn off all lights except the spotlight?
Please turn off the front light.
- This is good.
- Like this.
We'll go with this mood.
I had to intensely check everything, lights and all.
Do the ninja running pose.
That part.
(Practicing the choreography)
Again.
Seven and eight.
Again. Let's do it again.
Again.
Oh, my.
I can feel the tension.
It's like this.
(INGYOO demonstrates the move.)
I want it to be more like this. Do you get what I mean?
(Ting! Bralalala)
I want it to go like this, but right now...
(Dum, dan, dda)
This. No.
- Okay.
- Okay!
Slide. Again. Five.
Details to make us look like ninjas.
We created a good performance, so I wanted to do very well.
The concept is clear,
but I'm curious how it'll turn out.
We need one big bang.
You need people to go, "Oh, my!" to survive.
I was that confident.
INGYOO's mindset is really like,
"I will not lose."
He's determined to survive.
Hello.
We are always here.
Are The Stories here?
I think MIN JUN's will be fun.
MIN JUN has the power to make people look forward to his performance.
Yes.
I tried to line up the lights...
to the tone and timing of the performance.
Can you open it?
(Whipping open)
(Skillful)
It's like a torch.
Insane. That's an amazing idea.
(Satisfied)
The projection was good, the lights were good,
the choreography was good, and the formations were good.
What could it be?
The synopsis is intriguing, so I'm also curious about the costumes.
I felt our performance would be very cool.
I'm going to survive this Last Stage no matter what.
The biggest merit...
is that it's the third episode of Last Stage.
I think I'll be one of the two that survive.
We'll create an amazing performance...
that no one has ever seen before.
I'll push myself to the extreme...
and produce the best performance in my own style.
I want to dance soon.
I want people to see this soon.
Someone better than me? I don't think there is anyone.
(Last Stage: 24H)
The Directors' War of Choreographers,
where we go beyond performance and create works of art.
Out of the four choreographers standing at the edge of the cliff,
who will be the two who protect their names to the end?
This competition was made for me.
The girls will be all tears.
It'll be fun. It'll be very intense.
Please bring the right attitude...
- as we walk in.
- Okay.
- I'm a rose.
Okay.
We will now introduce the Fight Judges...
who will decide their fate.
(Excited)
The lineup of judges is actually the most important.
I'm most curious about the Fight Judges.
That wasn't that important to us.
A director who displays endless new possibilities...
with their out-of-the-box perspective.
Monika!
(Monika)
(Happy)
It's Monika.
Hello.
I'm so happy to see her now.
A choreographer who has created perfect performances.
A performance director who shines on stage and as an artist.
Shim Jae Won.
Next, a choreographer who captured the world's attention...
with their creative concepts and performances...
that no one else can replicate.
(Who?)
The creator and director who leads Avantgardey.
Akane.
Oh, is that Akane?
(Akane)
Oh, yes.
(The bubbly dance took over Japan in 2017.)
Japanese high school girl concept?
It's a dance team that wears all the same wigs...
and Japanese school uniforms and is very synchronized.
They put on performances...
that really capture the audience's attention.
(Director Akane perfects her performances...)
(with creative ideas and stage production.)
I wonder what sort of style Akane likes.
I was confident.
To entertain them.
Half excited and half nervous?
Because we got the best reaction during the run-through.
For this Last Stage: 24H,
all four choreographers started...
with the same amount of time and same conditions.
What makes the difference in their performances...
will be the perspective and interpretation...
each director brings to the given conditions.
Fight Judge Shim Jae Won,
what standards will you use to judge the performances today?
The intention of the director,
level of perfection, and expression.
I'll do my best to look at those in a balanced way.
There was a limited amount of time...
and an objet they had to use.
I imagine they must've had to utilize their experiences...
and backgrounds to think on their feet.
So I'll choose the director...
who has the best balance of all of those things...
and really does well.
She's so sharp that it almost feels cold.
(BADA, get it together.)
I highly value uniqueness.
And I also want to look at how the music and production...
are displayed together with the same sense of direction...
rather than those things going about on their own.
(Full of excitement)
What is clear is that it's hard for me to lose.
I'll definitely survive.
I'll come back alive once again.
I'll give it my all. Let's go.
Before the performances,
we have a special guest...
at Last Stage: 24H today.
The lead of the popular Netflix series,
"To All the Boys I've Loved Before..."
Hold on.
I'm not exaggerating. That's my favorite Netflix series.
And the action film...
that'll premiere this coming October,
"Street Fighter."
(Source: Lotte Entertainment)
It's Noah Centineo. Welcome.
(Fascinated)
Hello.
- Hello!
He's cute.
I heard there was this incredible dance competition show called...
"Street World Fighter."
The directors and dancers have...
incredible performances prepared for you.
I am so excited, and I cannot wait for you to see it.
(Us too)
Now, the choreographers...
to prove themselves with their names and creations.
The performances that'll determine their fates will begin now.
Which two directors...
will protect their name with just one performance?
Last Stage: 24H starts now.
Are you ready?
Fight!
The first director to start off Last Stage...
is BADA.
(It's BADA right off the bat!)
She must be nervous.
BADA created something so new and cool.
We finally get to see it.
Is their concept "The Rose of Versailles?"
I guess BADA is a princess after all.
Oh, so pretty.
White Rose is here.
(Bursting into laughter)
(I've never seen her like this.)
It's so funny to see her wearing a dress.
Oh, really?
(Spinning around doing princess bows)
I've never seen her like that.
Actually, it's a concept I've really wanted to do.
I really wanted to,
but cool, girl-crush concepts suit me well,
so I kept pushing this off.
But I thought of this as my last-ever chance and gave it a shot.
The concept of my Last Stage is "Bloom."
I chose the concept, "Bloom."
(During the first practice session, Gently flapping)
It's kind of like a flower.
I need a flower.
As soon as I saw the umbrellas, flowers came to mind.
Just because I went to Last Stage,
it doesn't mean I've wilted.
I have grown, and I can bloom once again.
This must be good to use in the performance.
Make a circle formation.
I think the kick is to create a huge flower bud.
Flower bud coming in. Excuse me.
Thank you.
I wanted it to look like flower petals blooming.
And the fact that I'm inside of it is the kick.
I, someone who doesn't seem to belong in there,
pops out?
That's the idea.
"But that's very new."
I wanted to make something like that.
I invited a queen.
(A special queen who'll join us for this performance)
Funky Y, who'll be our secret weapon...
and our Black Rose, will join us.
(Funky Y, the leader of MANNEQUEEN, the queens of queens)
I wanted to create this black rose, white rose theme.
I've always collaborated a lot with Funky Y.
During those collaborations, I felt we had chemistry.
I wanted to show that on stage,
so I cast Funky Y.
We're going to do this sort of makeup.
That's amazing. It'll be very strong.
That's a real princess.
I wanted our makeup to have some impact.
I just got my nails done too.
Like they were dyed with roses.
Hello.
To go with the flower theme,
I chose dresses with lots of layers.
I wanted them to be like wedding dresses.
I wanted them to look like flowers from above.
Can we cut even more from the back? The length?
We have lots of moves where we sit down and get back up.
I wanted to eliminate all possible issues.
So I cut each one.
Do you have any detailed ideas for the production...
in terms of the concept, direction, or references?
A vibrant festival?
I want to wear wedding dresses.
Very street-style.
I'm going to make a sort of bouquet.
I want to add in elements of old musicals.
Some elements like that.
At first, I wanted to do something very strong.
Something very strong. Something BADA-like.
But this time,
I wanted to do something happy.
I wanted to feel overwhelmed with joy...
even while dancing.
No matter what, I'm a flower.
I've grown, and I can bloom again.
It was my goal to make such a song.
Okay. Let's not get hurt today.
Let's finish off strong. Got it?
- Yes!
Let's put on a performance we won't regret. Got it?
Are you ready?
- Yes!
Okay. One, two, three!
- Woo, woo, woo!
Okay!
While I'm at Last Stage,
I'll use all parts of my body...
to fill this stage.
I'll bloom like a flower on this stage.
(We're excited.)
(Look at that determination.)
The Last Stage BADA prepared for 24 hours...
to protect her name to the end...
starts now.
Ready? Fight!
I'm curious to see how perfect of a performance she prepared.
We need to win.
Let's see how good they are.
People expect a lot from me.
I have to do my best.
(Bloom, Overall concept, A wilted flower blooming once again)
(Objet utilization strategy, Layer umbrellas to depict an unopened bud)
- Oh, my.
- Oh, my. What is that?
- Oh, a rose.
- Oh, my.
This is intense.
It looks like a field of roses.
Hey, this is insane.
I like it.
This is fun.
Oh, how pretty.
It's really like Madonna.
So pretty. It makes me angry.
The queen is here.
It's totally a musical.
Oh, I am a bit threatened.
It's a show.
(Amazing)
I think BADA is a genius.
This is seriously insane.
Let's go!
(Perfect teamwork)
Oh, BADA!
So pretty.
Let's go!
Okay. Jazz.
Oh, yes.
(Totally)
(Into it)
The production scale is huge.
I like that.
This is no joke.
Legend.
So pretty!
(The ending...)
(is insane.)
(Tatter, Lusher, Sowon, Kyma, Cheche, Funky Y, Kim Gyu Ri)
(Kim Ye Won, Kim Ye Won, Kim Ga Eun, Im Ga Eun, Jeong Yu Na, Park Su Bin)
(Ryu Da Yeon, Cho Yeong Seo, Yu Seung Ju, Park Seo Yeon)
(Han Ga Yeon, Oh Jeong Yeon, Cho Hye Won, Lee Se Hyeon, and more)
Oh, we're in trouble.
Everyone is out of it.
(BADA...)
(never disappoints.)
(BADA successfully finished the performance.)
(Filling up with a surge of emotions)
Don't cry!
- Don't cry!
(Tearing up)
She's crying.
(Watching BADA's performance made Simeez tear up.)
Why am I crying?
She worked so hard.
Because I know...
She's crying again. Oh, gosh.
Good job.
(We did well, Team BADA.)
(BADA shares her appreciation...)
(with the team members who did a good job.)
I cried because I was so happy.
Even if this is my last performance, I don't regret anything.
(The other teams send them a sincere round of applause.)
There's a reason she's successful.
Okay. We still have to focus.
Warm up. Keep moving.
We need to stay cool-headed. It's a competition.
I need to get it together.
I am going to survive no matter what.
How did this performance resonate...
with our three Fight Judges?
Now, let's hear the comments from our judges.
Even without knowing the synopsis,
the theme was very well communicated.
The opening flower bud scene left a strong impression.
It made me excited to see...
the rest of the performance.
I'm so happy to hear positive comments.
Your concept highlighted the contrast...
between black and white.
Even the dancers' hair had that contrast.
You placed many elements throughout the performance...
to make that contrast noticeable even at a glance.
I was a bit worried about your objet utilization.
(Nervous)
I was worried the cliché elements you expect...
with umbrellas might feel boring.
(I was worried?)
But actually, the song...
reminded me of Broadway musicals,
and it went well with everything.
So I feel you chose...
the appropriate strategy in that short amount of time.
I want to give you a high score.
I received high praise.
It felt like I was being rewarded.
Just the fact that you produced a performance with an image...
of BADA that was quite opposite of what we're familiar with...
was very moving for me.
Also, you did a good job in placing captivating images throughout,
by changing up the events with each phrase.
I was engrossed in the performance.
It was a performance...
that displayed the life you've lived until now...
and the life you'll live from now.
Thank you.
(Thank you.)
I did well. I did so well.
I don't have any regrets.
I'm going to survive no matter what.
(Good job!)
Ta-da!
(What is it?)
What is it?
I wanted to give you all a rose.
Thank you for being my roses.
This performance felt like a bouquet.
It felt like a gift, a bouquet.
Thank you so much.
(Touched)
Thank you.
You're the queen of surprises.
(One by one, Team BADA came together and became a bouquet.)
Let's take a picture holding the flowers.
We need to go to the next stage.
I'm going to go to the next level.
The next director who will put on their Last Stage...
is Simeez.
(A wave of cheers)
I think Simeez might be a bit similar to me.
(Let's go, Simeez!)
I think they're all wearing white for the projection.
Fight Judge Monika,
you and Simeez have seen each other...
throughout your long dance careers.
Please tell us a strength...
the Simeez you know has as a director.
I think Simeez's greatest strength...
is that she always keeps her word.
So I've never seen her not do something she said she'd do.
I expect her to do the same today.
Thank you.
(Excited)
I'll spread my wings on this stage.
Thank you.
(Let's go!)
When we first made the music,
the first thing that came to mind...
was the image of wings.
A fallen angel?
This is the BPM and vibe.
(Explaining the vibe she wants with reference music)
I thought of it as one of the characters to lead this story.
It's my Last Stage,
so I should take on the role of leading the story.
About our most important wing...
We're going to have it similar to this.
I wanted to use the umbrellas to express wings.
Instead of using a single umbrella,
I want to make something huge by piling them up.
When they open and close,
they could look like huge wings...
from a distance.
They're perfect wings.
It's my first time in the Last Stage,
but I've watched it twice from above.
I noticed that the person with more impactful moments...
had a better chance.
So I decided to create that impact using a projector and umbrellas.
(Creating a standout moment through storytelling)
(Exclaiming)
That's so cool.
(Being immersed)
The performance itself was just Simeez.
She's determined.
Her team was the first...
to impress me...
with a projector.
Our team all lost our minds there.
Since it's a fallen angel,
the first thing that came to mind was bloody tears.
I chose to have silver tears.
The dancers had bloody tears.
When I first thought about umbrellas,
I could see ourselves wearing hooded jackets.
There's a part...
I had to get beaten in the middle,
so I decided to wear white,
and I dressed the dancers in toned-down outfits.
She's wearing a hood.
Whenever Simeez wore a hood, she awakened.
The fact that she wore a hood meant...
she awakend.
Since I prepared for it thinking it was my last,
what I wanted most was to present something...
I could be myself.
The outfits are black and white.
I think she gave the contrast on purpose.
Everyone's wearing black and she's the only one in white.
(What will Simeez's Last Stage look like as she spreads her wings?)
("FALLEN ANGEL" Directed by Simeez)
(Performance by Team Simeez)
It's telling a story.
Will she enter an unknown world?
(Getting immersed)
She really is a master artist.
I think that's some kind of barrier.
I think that's a barrier.
(Exclaiming)
There are a lot of scenes.
There's the look.
This is nice.
(Exclaiming)
(She's surprised.)
(Eyes on the stage)
Nice!
She really used the projector well. She made them look like wings.
There are wings.
Nice!
The effects are amazing.
- Nice.
- She wants to come out.
I think she's expressing something like oppression.
Her emotional progression is...
(Kim Hwan, Nemo, Jeong Bum, Na Hyun, Hwee Yul, Eun Seo, Ji Yul, Hui Rim)
(So Hyun, Yeon Woo, Kim Eun Jin)
(Automatic applause)
It felt so refreshing.
I couldn't contain myself.
That feeling of being overwhelmed was different.
She did an amazing job.
- There were no mistakes.
- It was so cool.
Right. There were no mistakes.
Simeez did a great job.
It really messed with my head.
You have to get ready to get hyped.
We have to be sweating. I said we have to be sweating by 9:30pm.
Start sweating.
Work up a sweat.
What did the three Fight Judges...
think about the performance?
Let's hear their comments.
The projection mapping that created those massive wings...
was really impressive.
The way each person moved their umbrella...
felt almost like they were breathing.
It was so impressive how the umbrellas were delicately used.
I thought the use of the umbrellas...
really elevated the individual movements...
and brought a whole new level of detail to the music.
It was amazing.
The first thing I thought was that it felt refreshing.
I just did what I wanted to do.
I was satisfied...
because I showed them who I was.
As a director, I thought you did a great job...
conveying the different formations and concepts,
and I was completely immersed in the performance.
I thought there were a lot of clever choices...
that made the performance feel three-dimensional...
while also making the flat images stand out clearly.
You started with crossing the stage...
then coming into the center,
and I thought you used the projection element...
at a key moment.
I could really feel all the effort you put...
into making the performance as immersive as possible.
The dancers had such great chemistry,
and there were so many moments that felt like movie scenes,
which made the performance really dynamic.
Well done.
My elimination was at stake,
but when considering my performance, I thought I had a chance.
Personally, I think Simeez's performance...
stood out more than BADA's.
She used the props...
in a less conventional way.
It was nearly perfect.
I don't know. I think it's neck and neck.
(Simeez returns to the waiting room after the performance.)
Why is she crying so much?
What is it?
(Crying)
(Patting)
Why are you crying?
I think...
(I think I didn't do so well.)
I heard good comments.
- Shall we watch the next one?
- Okay.
- INGYOO's performance.
- We have to watch that one.
Well done, everyone!
(Well done!)
Let's watch it.
Let's watch INGYOO's performance!
Let's see how well he does.
The director to perform the last stage next...
is INGYOO.
Let's get it, Kim In Gyoo!
Let's go!
(Exclaiming)
He's covered in blood.
That's cool.
(They're looking forward to it.)
Let's go, INGYOO!
INGYOO's performances are always high quality,
so I was looking forward to it.
I have to win.
I will survive.
What did you want to show people...
as a director in the Last Stage?
Having fun?
In the end, this is a competition,
so we have to present performances to win.
But what I can do best...
is to enjoy it.
Through that, I want the judges and the audience...
to have fun as well.
Yes!
Something exciting and most fun.
Out of the four of us, I'm the best at having fun.
The overall concept is simple.
It's ninja.
But I didn't want to make it obvious.
Did you listen to the music?
I did.
- It's fine, isn't it?
- It was nice.
The song I'd like to request...
is an Amapiano track.
Amapiano...
is a style of music that's widely popular in South Africa.
It's a genre I really like.
I thought it would be new to just have an umbrella...
with that music.
But I needed an interesting concept.
(INGYOO plays the track for the Last Stage.)
That's great.
The music is great.
(In a trance)
There was a point...
when the music started sounding Asian.
Shall we go with ninja?
- Ninja.
- Let's go!
Let's do it.
A ninja who uses spells.
It made me think of "Demon Slayer."
I really like Thunderclap and Flash.
Thunder Breathing is the best.
I thought I could use that.
Try setting up the umbrellas unevenly.
Front and diagonal.
(Instant execution)
Try arranging them in a zigzag pattern.
(Using props to recreate ninja techniques from anime)
Show us that part.
Should I appear from there?
One, two, three, four.
Five.
No one can mix Amapiano with ninja.
Being able to blend these two...
is what what makes my directing strong.
Blending various things together...
and creating something new.
Also, I have fun...
when I make such new things.
I think INGYOO's concept really stands out too.
Right. Ninja.
It also goes well with WE DEM BOYZ.
That's something men like.
It gets our hearts racing.
How do you resist that?
INGYOO...
certainly is a genius.
I think INGYOO is the biggest threat to me.
Ninjas don't wear fancy clothes.
They have to stay hidden,
so they wear a head covering.
(Tearing and tearing)
(Tearing all the fabric)
We'll tie our sleeves and pant hems with strings.
This really shows our determination for the Last Stage.
It's so cool.
We look like ninjas.
- You look nice.
- Great.
How to be a ninja on a budget.
It'll be boring to wear just black for a performance.
So we put red body paint on...
to show that we're part of one big group.
(They put red contact lenses in too.)
(Transformation into ninjas complete)
Guys, let's sleep in once this is over.
You all did so well. We look awesome right now,
so let's have fun.
- Of course!
- Yes!
One, two, three!
- Let's go!
- You got this.
- Break a leg.
INGYOO is really talented,
so I can't help but feel threatened.
Good luck!
Let's go and crush it out there.
I don't care about winning.
I just want us to look amazing out there.
I can't wait to dance.
I want everyone to see our performance.
- Let's go!
- Yes!
This is INGYOO's Last Stage that he prepared for 24 hours.
- You got this!
- Good luck!
Let's go!
Ready, fight!
(Amaninjas, Overall concept, Ninjas' victory dance)
(Objet strategy, using umbrellas as swords and weapons)
(Performance by Team Ninja)
Nice.
It's the canyon.
- It's a good setup.
- It's very exotic.
They put up bars.
Awesome.
This is already so fun.
That's so sexy!
Only WE DEM BOYZ can do this.
You're killing it!
Gosh!
They're so good.
They're incredible.
How he set up the running formation is just...
This is crazy.
- Amazing.
- The direction is so classy.
Goodness.
Thunderclap and Flash!
Isn't that from "Demon Slayer?"
(This is insane!)
(Electric)
This is astonishing.
They put away the umbrellas.
This is incredible.
INGYOO, you crushed it.
So fantastic!
This is very WE DEM BOYZ. It's so fun.
(Team INGYOO Dancers Kamel, AHOB, Youngbin, Dophan, NOAN)
(HOJUN, LIL LAW, Kwon Moo Joon, Park Ye Seong, Kim Woo Seok,)
(Lee Woo Jae, Kim Hyun Soo, Jung Tae Min)
This was so fun. We were the best.
It'll be hard to beat me.
(Loving it)
(Amazing)
- That was so cool.
- It was great!
So awesome.
How did he come up with this in 24 hours?
I was so in awe.
You look so handsome!
He crushed it.
There was a certain wit only INGYOO could pull off.
I'm curious what the three Fight Judges...
thought of this performance.
Let's hear what the Judges have to say.
First of all, INGYOO, that was amazing.
The key point was to utilize the umbrellas.
And how each directors used them...
would be the real attraction of the direction.
But I thought you wouldn't need them at all.
It worked.
And you threw away the umbrellas, like you were proving my point.
That was just amazing.
Throwing them away was Akane's type.
They all got so much better after tossing the umbrellas.
And as for the choreography,
I was surprised to see how you used different dance techniques...
throughout the performance in a unique way.
Overall, it was amazing.
I really liked the lighting at the beginning.
The moment it began,
I got the sense that I was entering another world.
I was visiting a ninja castle.
And your use of projections was impressive.
I got the sense that...
you were trying to leave a big impact by using them once.
That alone was very impactful for me.
What was interesting was that your concept...
is ninjas, which are East Asian and can be somewhat oriental.
But you used African beats with Amapiano style.
It could've been a strange match,
but it made me wonder if I could've thought of this as well.
You put it together beautifully.
And some of your dancers on stage...
made the mistake of...
dropping their umbrellas from the start.
For me, mistakes don't really matter too much.
That's because I was still immersed.
That alone was meaningful for me.
INGYOO pulled an INGYOO.
Thank you for the performance.
I don't care much about mistakes either.
I care what happens after the mistake.
But after the mistake, the dancer...
kept on dancing like he was really holding a sword.
That pulled me back in.
The fact that you brought in a dancer with such skills...
shows how much talent you have, INGYOO.
I know you're much smarter...
than you let on, INGYOO.
And I think you showed another side of your genius today.
The entrances were very three-dimensional,
using follow spotlight.
It felt like I was in an animation,
and I couldn't look away.
I really appreciate how you put this together.
And you're very stylish, INGYOO.
I loved that she said I was stylish.
It was such an honor.
You did well.
Good job, INGYOO.
Way to go.
It's over.
- You did amazing!
- It's INGYOO!
(Shouting)
- Guys, great job. Bring it in.
- INGYOO!
We tied up the loose ends in there.
We put all that work into a minute and 30 seconds...
and blew people's minds in there!
That's all there is to it.
Great work, guys. I had so much fun.
Great work!
INGYOO pulled an INGYOO.
I still got it.
"Street World Fighter: Directors' War".
The last director to present their Last Stage...
is JEONG MIN JUN.
(Finally)
(He's here!)
At last.
Gosh.
I'm most worried about MIN JUN.
He became the master of the Last Stage.
(JEONG MIN JUN steps onto the stage.)
(He's wearing something peculiar today as usual.)
I wonder what his concept is.
(The crowd is shocked by his strange attire.)
He cut up his clothes too much.
But it suits him somehow.
Once this performance is over,
the winner and loser will be determined.
As a director, what's the one thing you want to show...
in this Last Stage?
There are so many stories I love.
And I want to be a director...
that conveys those stories...
to the people watching.
If you watch all the performances I've made so far,
there's always drama it.
There's a plot.
For the first Last Stage,
I used a historic battle as motivation.
For the second one,
there was a bit of desperation.
And I tried to use that in the performance.
I think the director's job is to...
convey the narrative to the viewers...
and make them understand.
In that sense, I really put in a lot of work.
I'm sure MIN JUN has a plan.
Yes, I thought it through this time.
I knew I'd be on the Last Stage.
What's the concept this time?
"The Odyssey".
(That's MIN JUN.)
- Gosh.
- You're so trendy.
I recently watched the film, "The Odyssey,"
and I was really inspired by it.
I just knew I had to make it the concept...
for the Last Stage.
Who wants to try this?
Hold the umbrella and do a sword fight.
The first image I had...
with an umbrella was weapons.
And since I had to use many umbrellas,
it made me think of an army.
That led me to the concept of war.
First, you open the umbrella...
and huddle.
We're going to make a shape like the Trojan horse.
Since we're going with "The Odyssey,"
I thought we'd have to use the Trojan horse at some point.
And if we positioned the umbrellas to look like the horse...
and used a projector...
to shoot wooden textures onto the umbrellas,
with tree rings and whatnot...
And if we had human silhouettes showing...
in between the shape,
I'm sure the people would think...
that it's the Trojan horse.
I've been talking with the musical director as well.
I want drums to go wild...
at some point.
I think at first, we could take it steady...
until the middle.
And we could make it blow up in the end.
I wanted to utilize military-type beats...
like in "The Odyssey" into the song.
- Let's see.
- It's much nicer, right?
- It really is.
- Good.
I wanted ancient Northern European styles for hair and makeup as well.
"The Odyssey" is set in ancient times.
I wanted to portray that in the costume.
(He changes into the costume.)
(Exclaiming)
You look like a rich beggar.
What is this concept?
It's "The Odyssey".
So I kept the hair and makeup to a minimum.
- I want to look like a wanderer.
- Wanderer, got it.
You'll look cool once you get into your performance.
I just want to put on a great performance,
and connect with the audience with my performance.
I'm sure I can make it happen.
JEONG MIN JUN prepared this Last Stage...
for 24 hours to survive this competition.
Ready?
Fight!
- Let's go!
- We love you!
(Let's go, JEONG MIN JUN!)
(Flipping)
(Startled)
(They're turning the umbrellas inside out.)
- They're holding it differently.
- I like that they turned it over.
I know, right?
(What performance will they show us with the upturned umbrellas?)
This is my third Last Stage.
I think I mastered it at this point.
I'll have an edge.
(Odyssey, Overall concept, The story of Odysseus' war)
(Objet stragegy, reflecting light and forming a Trojan horse)
(Performance by Team JEONG MIN JUN)
(Surprised)
- This is legendary.
- It looks so cool.
MIN JUN is killing it.
That's his trademark move!
That's incredible.
(Engrossed)
It's like a film.
This is amazing.
He's being taken.
(Team JEONG MIN JUN Dancers)
(JYOS, Noah Im, Heejae, Jaeyoon, Jungmin, HAN, Harang, KUNA,)
(GUMA, Kwon Ian, Hasom, EVE, murphy, Go Ara)
(Cheering fills the entire set.)
(Exclaiming)
That was amazing.
Respect!
Gosh.
I did it. I'm so glad it went just the way I imagined.
MIN JUN was too good. I'm really worried.
MIN JUN is definitely going to survive again.
What did...
the three Fight Judges think of this performance?
Let's hear their comments right now.
First of all, I think your direction capability is amazing.
You can't get people to cheer this loudly otherwise.
And I have a nickname for you, MIN JUN.
Intro Genius.
You're an Intro Genius.
(A unique intro like no other)
You're truly an artist.
It was such an amazing performance.
Picturing it in your head...
and succeeding in bringing it to life are two different things.
Amazing work.
I was so glad she noticed my hard work.
I was elated.
What I first noticed...
while watching your performance was...
your desire to move the audience's feelings.
That's what made this more impressive.
Thank you.
The most creative use of the objets...
was the Trojan horse,
and the human silhouette after that.
I was really impressed with that.
But I did have some disappointments.
The way you expressed your ideas was creative,
but because you had such a firm idea for it,
I kept watching while wondering what it meant.
I thought it was a little superficial...
to portray the concept of the Odyssey.
Thank you.
- You did well.
- Well done.
MIN JUN finished his third Last Stage.
Please give it up for MIN JUN...
for this incredible performance.
(You did...)
(so well!)
- Good job!
- Well done!
BADA!
Good work.
Whatever the outcome,
I did my very best, so I have no regrets.
I felt liberated.
The competition of "Street World Fighter: Directors' War"...
is coming to an end.
It's terrifying, really.
My hands get all sweaty.
I can't lose anyone.
No one deserves to go home.
(The 4 directors come on stage after their performance.)
Good job!
- Great work!
- Yes!
These directors have gone through many missions...
and two Last Stages...
for the position of the best director.
After their fierce competition,
these four directors stand at a crossroads of survival again.
Only two directors...
will survive today to make it to the semi-finals.
You're crying!
Why am I crying? I was overwhelmed.
Could I have a tissue? I didn't feel very confident.
My competitors were too great,
and I wasn't sure if I could beat them.
The anxiety is always there.
(Sighing)
My heart keeps pounding.
If you had fun, it's all good.
I want to go with INGYOO or Hee Jung.
I thought differently.
One of them used such an unexpected layout...
and really impressed me.
BADA's performance was the most polished.
I don't want to say it was ordinary,
but I have seen that direction somewhere before.
Wait a second. Let me ask you a question.
BADA had better quality,
but Hee Jung was the one who challenged herself.
I think Akane is looking at this in a different way than Monika,
and I admit I'm looking at this in another way too.
(The judges needed a lot of time.)
The last stage before the finals, the semi-finals.
Who will be the two directors...
to put their names on that stage?
I really want to win for the sake of my team.
I felt really free at first.
And I was taking it easy.
I had fun, so it's all good. I was satisfied.
The third Last Stage: 24H.
The first survivor is...
This is terrifying.
I really have no idea.
(Tension fills the studio.)
Director...
(Director...)
(Who is the first survivor to make it to the semi-finals?)
BADA.
(It's Director BADA.)
(The first survivor is BADA.)
I knew at first sight that it was a flower bud,
and I liked how she used each umbrella...
as a flower petal.
It was a very high-quality performance.
BADA's the one who used the objets...
- to the fullest.
- That's right.
The BADA we knew used to do...
androgynous performances.
Putting on a feminine performance must've been...
a huge challenge for her.
And she even managed to make it perfect.
You're right.
First, I want to thank the amazing three directors...
who put on the Last Stage with me.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll show you more amazing...
and more BADA-like performances in the future.
Thank you!
Congratulations, BADA.
Well done.
You did so well.
I felt so sorry for the others that I made it...
to the next round safely on my own first.
We all put in so much work together.
I felt guilty, since we all did our best.
There is only one spot left in the semi-finals.
What will happen to the remaining three?
I will announce the first director to be eliminated...
in the third Last Stage: 24H.
Now it's a 33 percent chance.
I did what I wanted to do,
and I showed them who I am.
I was willing to accept my fate.
MIN JUN's direction was off the charts,
but if you look at the overall structure, mine was grander.
I was feeling good.
I was sure I'd pass this round.
"Street World Fighter: Directors' War".
The first director to be eliminated from the third Last Stage is...
It is JEONG MIN JUN.
(First eliminated choreographer, JEONG MIN JUN)
(Eliminated choreographer, JEONG MIN JUN)
(Shocking)
The expressive quality is really good,
but unless you look at the synopsis, it's hard to follow along...
It falls a bit short when it comes to expressing that aspect itself.
Since he has such a strong worldview,
I feel like he didn't choose more intuitive ways to express it.
However, though,
the fact that MIN JUN kept doing the same sort of thing every time,
bothered me a little.
Being a director isn't just about excelling in one area.
It requires proficiency across multiple aspects.
So, when the concepts remain consistently similar,
- the director's capabilities...
- You lack competence.
tends to come across as a shortcoming.
Please share a few final words.
(Third Last Stage: 24H Final elimination, MIN JUN)
(Well...)
For me...
this Last Stage was especially meaningful...
because the movie I watched...
with others was "Odyssey." But...
I personally cherished the conversations...
we shared after that,
and I really want to say that it was such a happy experience for me.
To be honest, when I first appeared on this program, I really hoped...
given that I work as a co-director for the team "The Stories,"
was that the competition scene I love so much...
would become known to a wider audience was my expectation.
I wondered if appearing on the show would really help get the word out.
I was quite worried about it,
but looking back, I feel I was able to show so much...
by participating in this program.
And ultimately, I feel I've shown...
the kind of director I am...
and the type of work I create,
so I think I've achieved everything I set out to do on this program.
The stories I'll be writing from here on out are...
just beginning,
so I hope you'll stay tuned.
(Please stay tuned for MIN JUN's new stories.)
Well done.
You did well. Really.
You know you did great, right?
(Well done, youngest one.)
(Eliminated choreographer, JEONG MIN JUN)
This is too hard, seriously.
Now, only the results for the last two people remain.
The final director to survive from...
"Street World Fighter: Directors' War Last Stage: 24H"...
and to advance to the semi-finals is...
(Last Stage: 24H, Simeez vs. INGYOO)
I think it's Simeez.
I think it was fantastic.
If they don't mind making mistakes, I think they'd choose INGYOO.
The introduction at the beginning was very good.
And I think he used the objet with more sensitivity.
I thought, "I'd win."
Whatever. Come what may.
(Which director will advance to the semi-finals...)
(after conquering the last stage?)
It is INGYOO.
(The second survivor, INGYOO)
Congratulations, INGYOO.
(Third Last Stage: 24H Final elimination, Simeez)
It struck the perfect balance...
between an oriental aesthetic and a trendy vibe.
Plus, you couldn't tell at all that he made a mistake with the umbrella.
When it comes to making the most of the stage and the lighting,
he was the first, to be honest.
If you ask whose work I'd like to see more of in the future,
I think it would be INGYOO's.
(They were once a team, but their destinies diverged.)
(Good job.)
Still, I'm happy to have achieved this result...
thanks to the judges appreciating...
the performance.
But it feels a bit sad...
to lose the colleagues I enjoyed dancing and working with.
She described it as a transformation from an angel into a devil,
- but it didn't resonate with me.
- It didn't click.
I certainly understood the angel image,
but the way the transformation played out wasn't very convincing.
Instead of focusing on the performance itself,
the sense of anxiety and tension came through so strongly.
And it was actually a bit uncomfortable to watch.
You know, the missions I faced during the show...
actually involved the kind of work...
I've always dealt with.
But what made it different was...
having comrades by my side.
I learned a lot, relied on them,
and shared the challenges together.
I'm truly happy and grateful for that experience.
If viewers can at least come to understand...
what a director actually does...
I think concept is the most important.
And that it involves handling a wide range of elements...
beyond just choreography,
if people could understand that,
then I think I've made the right decision to make the appearance.
If asked, whether I want to be a good choreographer or director,
I'd choose being a good director. That feels right to me.
I feel that being a good director is...
a role defined by the recognition of...
the people who worked right alongside me in the field.
I hope that for my coworkers, I remain a fond memory...
and a positive influence,
and that I also leave a lasting impression on the audience.
I believe this reflects the qualities of a top director.
I've blossomed into a top director.
You've worked very hard. Keep up the great work.
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(National Tour Concert Information)
Why are you crying?
You've done a good job. Keep it up.
- Simeez.
- BADA.
- What do I do from now on?
- No.
BADA, show them the power of women!
What are you saying? I can only do that if you are here.
(Eliminated choreographer, Simeez)
Street World Fighter: Directors' War...
(The highly anticipated semi-final mission)
It is the brand performance film mission.
- iPhone?
- It's the commercial, isn't it?
That is incredible.
Are we filming it ourselves?
This is really crazy.
You will serve as a director...
while also acting as an official model for a global smartphone brand.
(Incredible)
I really wanted to be in a smartphone commercial before.
That was my dream.
I really want to be chosen as the director.
(Gosh)
I've never wanted something so bad.
(I really wanted it.)
(This is awesome.)
This is something of great pride for me.
(I really have to do this.)
This is such a huge benefit, really.
Wouldn't you want to try shooting that commercial at least once?
(What a great scale, this is.)
Now, I truly have no regrets.
I truly have no regrets. But just this one thing.
(Model?)
(You have got to do it.)
(The five choreographers will each produce a solo performance film.)
(Three judges will select one Movement Director.)
We will select only one Movement Director.
I'm confident with my final result.
I really want the director's position.
(I really want to do it.)
I am so confident to do well.
(This is good.)
I can create the best result.
I have no concerns...
and I want to showcase my unique identity.
(I'm really confident.)
It looks like Kasper is trying out something different.
(It's not for me.)
There were movements that I do not prefer.
I thought that was really bad.
I don't know how I'm perceived by them, but...
(I want to break that.)
Are you thinking that everyone will do the arm movements together, too?
You know, that thing he always does.
(Flapping arms)
I don't think it would look cool if INGYOO and I did it.
I can already picture exactly what Koo Young is going to do.
Exploding from a single small energy...
and expanding into tremendous energy.
(I still don't quite understand it intuitively.)
(It's completely different...)
(from the vibe I had in mind.)
I becomes the energy itself.
(It's a bit old.)
It's like I ordered Iced Americano" but...
(Instead of coffee beans...)
(he put in beans for injeolmi.)
It's going to turn into roasted grain powder.
(Global smartphone brand model)
This is such a huge benefit.
I came back from the fire pit.
It's time for me to turn things over.
Only one gets...
(Last Stage: 24H Revealing one person to be saved)
(The three who aren't exempted...)
(will be confirmed for the Last Stage.)
I should be the one director...
who advances straight to the finals.
I think there's a good chance of winning...
(Goodness)
Koo Young has to go to the Last Stage.
It's about time he goes.
(He has to go, given public sentiment.)
I said to Koo Young...
(You should go to the Last Stage once.)
Anyone who's been to Last Stage...
would be absolutely green with envy with Koo Young...
(Won't let him go easily.)
I have no thoughts about the Last Stage.
(I won't be going.)
(Movement Director)
Where is he going?
Is that Koo Young's room?
He's going into Koo Young's room.
He's going to Koo Young.
(What do we do?)
Is Koo Young the only one that survives?
Gosh. I should prepare for the Last Stage quickly.
I'm going to the Last Stage.
I don't want to go to the Last Stage.
Result for the single finalist advancing to the finals.
Director Back Koo Young's next directing is...
(Last Directing Credit Board Director Back Koo Young)
The Final Survival Directing Battle...
"Last Stage: 24H."
Four years ago, during "Street Man Fighter,"
I was eliminated at this exact stage...
and failed to reach the finals.
Here and now, I will prove...
why I have survived this long.
I will prove myself.
The director who will claim the final spot in the finals...
In the end, I'm the one who's going to win.